the world would be a better place if
everybody had a perfect deadlift don't
you think
you're about to see the best set of
steps for that perfect deadlift you've
ever seen
step one approach the bar so that your
shins are one inch away from the barbell
putting it directly over the middle of
your foot step two
without bending your shins to the
barbell grab the barbell
just on the outside of your shins do not
move the barbell step three push your
knees forward
until your shins meet the barbell
dropping your hips
down into position step four push your
chest through and pull your shoulders
down towards your hips
step five push your knees out into your
forearms
and drag the barbell directly up your
legs keeping it in contact all the way
until you're standing straight up and
down then push your hips back
and lower the bar down the floor keeping
it in contact with your legs the entire
time
and that my friends is how you do a
perfect deadlift i'ma keep the content
coming
follow for more